Hello, Bubble!
Hey, Leafy!
Since you are so wonderful,
I'm giving you a gift!
Wow! That's the nicest thing
anyone's ever done for me!
Don't open it, Bubble!
I-It could be a trap!
[sharp inhale] I can do what I want!
Ooh! They're the Springy Shoes I've always wanted!
Thanks, Leafy!
You're welcome.
Hey! I want a gift!
- Oh, uhhhm... well- ahh, well...
- Gimme!
- Here!
- Gee, thanks!
Ahhh!
Ice Cube, I got some for you too!
Wha? Thanks!
Hey! Those are mine!
[INTRO PLAYS]
Subtitles: TAFFYMARZI
Let's do Cake at Stake.
So, as the nine of you know,
all of you are up for elimination.
Except for me!
Yes, Firey, except for you.
So now it's time to see who will be eliminated.
Announcer:
We've got a large crowd watching us again. Stalkers.
However, one may join the game.
Everyone:
Gasp!
But I'll get to that later.
We have 288 votes.
Anyway, here are 8 knives.
If you are safe, I'll throw you a knife.
I'm not sure if I want to be safe!
So first, Firey had immunity so he's safe. Fling.
Wuh!
Also, Ice Cube only had 5 votes.
She is safe. Fling.
Ahhhh!
Announcer:
Bubble and Leafy got 7 and 10 votes respectively.
What a relief!
Hup!
Announcer:
Spongy. Despite your extreme fatness,
you only received 28 votes.
Buh...
On April 1st 2011, history was made.
Englishcreamcakes cast the first vote EVER for Pencil.
Oh no, seriously?!
It turns out she got 37 other votes, too.
Regardless, with only 38 votes, Pencil is safe. Fling.
That's 38 more votes than I expected!
So it's Tennis Ball, Blocky, or Rocky, to be eliminated.
Well, it's not Rocky. Fling.
[SLOW-MO]
Bleh!
And it's not Tennis Ball. Fling.
Ahhhhhhhh!
Blocky, I'm sorry, but you received 112 votes.
That's enough to eliminate you, again.
No! You can't eliminate me!
I-I'm like the star of the show!
Blocky:
Ahhhh!
So Blocky has been eliminated.
Let's take some time to
commemorate Blocky's elimination.
No! Pssh. Let's not do that.
I agree! Let's not.
Fine. Whatever. I guess Blocky gets no love.
Anyway, you are the final 8.
Yay! Being in the final 8 without Coiny is wonderful!
8 is also 2 to the 3rd!
For your information, these are your current scores.
At the end of this episode, the 3 people
with the lowest scores will be up for elimination.
Now it's time to start the 17th contest.
We will be throwing frisbees.
Ooh, yay!
Eh!
But before we can begin, you must pair up.
Uhh, pair up? Okay.
OMG, Bubble, we so, like, have to be partners!
Yeah!
Wha?
Oh, sorry, Ice Cube. I'd let you in if I could, but I can't.
Gagh!
Revenge!
Hmmm... Ah hah!
Leafy:
Ice Cube, come on down, you can be my ally!
Thanks for picking me! Pencil
wouldn't let me into her alliance.
You are in our alliance Icy, just not right now.
Bleh!
Well, the gross ones are in a team,
so I-I guess I'm with you, Tennis Ball.
So are you done forming teams?
Everyone:
Yeah!
Each team gets a Frisbee.
Stay on opposite sides of the zone.
Try to have three successful catches.
Ooh! That might not be so easy!
But if you don't finish before the Sun goes down...
You.
Will.
Incur.
A PENALTY.
Go.
Okay, ready?
Ready!
- Ugh...
- Sorry!
Come on, Ice Cube! Let's get first!
Leafy:
Gasp!
Bleh!
Throw harder!
Yuh!
Hurgh!
Wow! That was amazing!
Hueh!
I know, right?
Oh no! Your saliva is too sticky!
Do I want to recover a
recently destroyed Ice Cube? Yes.
When was the ice cube destroyed?
Around 22 seconds ago.
What were the dimensions of the Ice Cube?
8 by 9 by 11.
Buh!
Hmph!
Hurry! Hurry! Hurry! The other teams are catching up!
I'm trying!
Alliance power!
Yeah, Bubble! Air five!
Firey:
Tennis Ball! Hurry! Now!
Hmm.... tap water, I believe?
Yeah! We're done!
- Bleh!
- Ommm!
Yaaay! We finished!
Two teams have finished.
Two have not.
And what do you know?
The sun is setting.
Ennngh!
Here! I'll get another frisbee!
Haannhahhaannngh...
Hueh!
Hnnnngh!
Hurry!
Hueh!
Phew! That's three!
Wow, that was too close.
Okay, final question. What was the Ice Cube's personality?
Hmm... I'd say quiet and vengeful.
Yay! Ice Cube! Now get to the other side...
...and catch this frisbee!
Noooo!
That's the end. Ice Cube and Leafy will receive a penalty.
Well, that was a short night.
Now it's time to receive your rewards.
First, Ice Cube, for receiving the
fewest votes at this Cake at Stake, you get a prize.
[beautiful harp music plays]
[applause]
Congratulations, Ice Cube!
Announcer:
Pencil and Bubble were the first to finish their catches.
Ooh, let's see what we get!
[beautiful harp music plays]
[applause]
OMG, yay!
[applause dies down]
What'd we get?
[beautiful harp music plays]
[applause]
Meh.
[applause continues]
Okay, Tennis Ball, here it is.
[beautiful harp music plays]
[faint applause]
It's not much, but I guess I'll take it.
Let's add those up.
Announcer:
Ice Cube and Leafy, you received a penalty.
Ohh, let's see what it is.
[beautiful harp music plays]
[huge applause]
Hey guys! For a prank,
Blocky:
suspend the Firey Recovery Center above a lake.
It's simple!
Blocky:
Idea by Simondomino and Geriolah7!
Voiceover:
This program was brought to you by
Blocky's Funny Doings International.
Leafy and Ice Cube, you each lost 1,000 points.
Announcer:
So these are your current scores.
Tennis Ball, Ice Cube, and Leafy are in the danger zone.
But the voters won't be deciding who will be eliminated.
The contestants will.
Everyone:
Gasp!
Announcer:
The five contestants who aren't in the danger zone
will have one month to choose who to eliminate.
Ooh, ha hah! Finally some control!
But what will the voters vote on?
Well, it turns out that one
recommended character will join the game.
Everyone:
Gasp!
We need help deciding which one.
Thirty characters were hand-picked out of hundreds.
Here they are.
I don't have a favorite number. I really don't.
Ba-ah-hoh! Ah-ah-hohleh!
[bag rips]
[barf leaks out of bag]
Tennis balls aren't the only ones with lines!
[ding]
OH NO, FIREY, YOU LIT MY FUSE!
I'm a dictionary and you better believe it!
Watches are wannabes.
[thunder and lightning strikes]
[demonic-like voice]
AW, SERIOUSLY?!
[speaking unintelligibly fast]
[cracks]
[BM!]
I hate you!
[eating fries]
[rustles]
I have a tattoo.
[nails on Woody]
Woody:
Ahhhhh!
[deep voice]
I am the new Coiny!
[explodes]
[breathes]
Vote for me or I'll crush you!
-... ..-. -.. ..
Please, please, please!
Can I join the game?! Please, please-
[saws on Woody]
Woody: Ahhhh!
[leaves rustle]
♪ Dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah ♪
♪ Cake at Stake! ♪
Voters, comment to vote who you think should
join the battle. Voting ends May 10th.
Everyone in TLC:
Ahhhh!